Matthias Wens

Staf van elzenlaan 30, 2550 Kontich, Belgium +32497 28 23 22 | matthias_wens@hotmail.com

PROFILE

Name: Matthias Wens

Address: Staf van elzenlaan 30, 2550 Kontich, Belgium

• Phone: +32 497 28 23 22

• E-mail: matthias_wens@hotmail.com

• Date of birth: 22-08-1995

• Place of birth: Wilrijk, Belgium

Nationality: Belgian

• Gender: Male

• Marital Status: Single

PROFILE

I am an engaged student in Master of Electronics and ICT Engineering Technology at KULeuven. I have an advanced skillset in Python programming and have leadership experiences. I am currently searching for a student job in python or java developing.

EDUCATION

KULeuven, Campus De Nayer

Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium

Master of Electronics and ICT Engineering Technology (not yet finished)

2014-2018

Bachelor of ICT Engineering (not finished)

Heverlee, Belgium 2013-2014

Sint-ritacollege

Kontich, Belgium

Grieks-wiskunde

KULeuven

2007-2013

EXPERIENCE

/

OTHER EXPERIENCE

E-kring

Sint-katelijne-waver, Belgium

Chief of Course documents store (Cursusdienst)

2016-2017

- Communication with professors and assistants.
- Making sure that fellow-students receive printed course documents after they ordered and paid for them.
- Participating in the meetings of the center-group of the organization (Praesidium).
- Helping with built-up, clean-up, ... of activities.

Schoolrock Festival

Kontich, Belgium

Coördinator 2012-2013

- Leading function in the organisation of Schoolrock Festival, a festival organised by approximately 90 students of Sint-ritacollege, Kontich, Belgium
- Follow up the different working groups of students.
- Leading the meetings of the center-group of the organization.
- Participate in meetings with police, fire department, municipality, mayor, school principal, ...
- Coordinate the different events during the building of the festival, the festival itself and the clean-up afterwards.

Schoolrock Festival

Kontich, Belgium

Co-operator Terrain unit / Chief of Main Entrance

2011-2012

- Participating in meeting of the working group "Terrein".
- Placing orders for stages, Pa installations, ...
- Responsible for the Entrance, Personal search and Ticketing control during the Festival. Leading function over approximately 20 students.
- Participate in built-up and clean-up of the festival.

SKILLS

- Dutch (Mother language)
- Good understanding of both written and spoken English
- Conversational in French

- Holding a full car driver's license.
- Advanced level skills in Microsoft Office Suite/Libre Office.
- Programming: Python2/3 (99%), Java (95%), SQL (75%), HTML (90%), CSS (85%),
 Assembly (80%), VHDL (100%), C (80%), JavaScript (85%), PHP (85%), XML (85%), ...

HONOR & AWARD

Winner of Google Hashcode in the Antwerp Hub

Antwerp, Belgium

Google (Hosted by Taglayer)

2017

Winner of the online qualification round of Google Hashcode in the Antwerp Hub.

OTHER

Kazou vzw Antwerp, Belgium

Animator 2011-now

Accompany and animate children aged 15-16 on a vacation.

Creactief vzw Mortsel, Belgium

Swimming Instructor 2011-now

Teaching children (Ages 4-14) to swim

Judoclub Kim-budo Kontich, Belgium

Judo assistant Trainer 2010-now

Helping the trainer with the judo trainings.

Training the youngest group of judoka's.

HOBBY

- Rock climber
- Pianist and guitarist